<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>George Vanburgh</title><link>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on George Vanburgh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 14:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twitch Chat Scraper FAQ</title><link>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/twitch-chat-scraper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/twitch-chat-scraper-faq/</guid><description>Recently, a side-project I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on to scrape Twitch chat logs has been causing quite a lot of confusion, both on Twitch and Twitter. I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a follow-up post detailing exactly what it is I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to, but in this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll attempt to summarise some of the most frequently asked questions, and my responses to them.
Who are you? As my Twitter explains, I&amp;rsquo;m a final-year Computer Science student at the University of Manchester.</description></item><item><title>"Hacking" Amazon Dash Buttons in the UK</title><link>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/hacking-amazon-dash-buttons-in-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 13:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/hacking-amazon-dash-buttons-in-the-uk/</guid><description>Love them or loath them, Amazon Dash buttons are pretty cool little devices. What most people consider to be nothing more than a simple way to stock up on Gatorade and nappies are actually one of the cheapest 802.11b/g/n devices on the market - which makes them an extremely interesting proposal for home automation.
By now, videos and blog posts of people abusing the low-low price of $5/button for their own ends are all over the internet.</description></item><item><title>Using Jenkins as Part of a Latex Workflow</title><link>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/using-jenkins-as-part-of-a-latex-workflow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.georgevanburgh.co.uk/posts/using-jenkins-as-part-of-a-latex-workflow/</guid><description>LaTeX is a fantastic, sometimes forgotten typesetting system - with a radically different workflow compared to most WYSIWYG editors. The fact that, in LaTeX, what you edit (a .tex file), and what you produce (typically a .pdf or .ps file) are totally different files can take a bit of getting used to. This idea of treating &amp;lsquo;documents as source-code&amp;rsquo; has some powerful benefits, however. Many people already use VCS as a repository for storing LaTeX markup - which has numerous benefits when it comes to managing multiple different versions of a document, and writing with multiple contributors.</description></item></channel></rss>